A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1940-1946 FA758
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1945
  - Nicaragua, 1945; 1945/325
    - Nicaragua - Nursing, 1945; 1945/325.C
      - Nicaragua, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2054)
  - Panama, 1945; 1945/327
    - Panama - Malaria, 1945; 1945/327.I
      - Panama, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2054)
    - Panama - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/327.R
      - Panama, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2054)
    - Panama - Tuberculosis, 1945; 1945/327.T
      - Panama, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2054)
  - Paraguay, 1945; 1945/329
    - Paraguay - Nursing, 1945; 1945/329.C
      - Paraguay, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2054)
    - Paraguay - Malaria, 1945; 1945/329.I
      - Paraguay, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2054)
  - Peru, 1945; 1945/331
    - Peru, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2054)
    - Peru, 1945 (Box 302, Folder 2055)
  - Venezuela, 1945; 1945/339
    - Venezuela, 1945 (Box 303, Folder 2056)
    - Venezuela, 1945 (Box 303, Folder 2057)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/339.D
      - Venezuela, 1945 (Box 303, Folder 2058)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1945 (Box 303, Folder 2058)
  - Great Britain, 1945; 1945/400
    - Great Britain, 1945 (Box 303, Folder 2058)
  - England, 1945; 1945/401
    - England - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 303, Folder 2059)
    - England - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 303, Folder 2060)
    - England - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 303, Folder 2061)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/401.A
      - England, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2062)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/401.E
      - England, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2062)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/401.R
      - England, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2062)
      - England, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2063)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/401.S
      - England, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2063)
      - England - Nuffield College, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2064)
  - Ireland, 1945; 1945/403
    - Ireland, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2065)
    - Ireland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/403.E
      - Ireland, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2065)
  - Scotland, 1945; 1945/405
    - Scotland, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2065)
    - Scotland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/405.D
      - Scotland, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2065)
    - Scotland - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/405.R
      - Scotland, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2065)
  - Wales, 1945; 1945/407
    Wales
    - Wales, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2066)
  - Malta, 1945; 1945/409
    - Malta, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2066)
  - Australia, 1945; 1945/410
    - Australia, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2066)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1945; 02.1945/410.A
      - Australia, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2066)
    - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/410.R
      - Australia, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2066)
    - Australia - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/410.S
      - Australia, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2066)
  - New Zealand, 1945; 02.1945/418
    - New Zealand, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2066)
  - Fiji, 1945; 1945/419
    - Fiji, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2066)
  - Caribbean Region, 1945; 1945/420
    - Carribbean Region - Administration, 1945 (Box 304, Folder 2067)
    - Carribbean Region, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2068)
  - Guyana, 1945; 1945/423
    - Guyana, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2069)
    - Guyana - Malaria, 1945; 1945/423.I
      - Guyana, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2069)
  - Honduras, 1945; 1945/425
    - Honduras, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2069)
  - Canada, 1945; 1945/427
    - Canada - Administration, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2070)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2071)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/427.A
      - Canada, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2072)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1945; 1945/427.C
      - Canada, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2072)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/427.E
      - Canada, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2072)
    - Canada - Public Health Education, 1945; 1945/427.L
      - Canada, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2073)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/427.R
      - Canada, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2073)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/427.S
      - Canada, 1945 (Box 305, Folder 2073)
  - Bermuda, 1945; 1945/430
    - Bermuda - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/430.E
      - Bermuda, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
  - St. Vincent, 1945; 1945/431
    - St. Vincent, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
    - St. Vincent - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/431.A
      - St. Vincent, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
  - Bahamas, 1945; 02.1945/433
    - Bahamas - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/433.A
      - Bahamas, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
  - Barbados, 1945; 1945/435
    - Barbados - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/435.E
      - Barbados, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
  - Jamaica, 1945; 1945/437
    - Jamaica, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
    - Jamaica - Nursing, 1945; 1945/437.C
      - Jamaica, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
    - Jamaica - Yellow Fever, 1945; 1945/437.O
      - Jamaica, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
  - Leeward Islands, 1945; 1945/439
    - Leeward Islands - Malaria, 1945; 02.1945/439.I
      - Leeward Islands, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
  - Dominica, 1945; 1945/443
    - Dominica, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
  - Trinidad, 1945; 1945/451
    - Trinidad, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2074)
  - India, 1945; 1945/464
    - India - (A-B), 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2075)
    - India - Bhore Committee Reports, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2076)
    - India - Bhore Committee Reports, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2077)
    - India - Bhore Committee Reports, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2078)
    - India - Bhore Committee Reports, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2079)
    - India - Bhore Committee Reports, 1945 (Box 306, Folder 2080)
    - India - (C-Z), 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2081)
    - India - (C-Z), 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2082)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/464.A
      - India, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2083)
    - India - Nursing, 1945; 1945/464.C
      - India, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2083)
      - BUC-1 Buchanan, Edith "Outline of a Proposed Programme for an Endowed Independent School of Nursing in Delhi, India", 1945 (Box 562, Folder 3828)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/464.D
      - India, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2083)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/464.E
      - India, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2083)
    - India - Yellow Fever, 1945; 1945/464.O
      - India, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2083)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/464.S
      - India, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2083)
  - Iraq, 1945; 1945/470
    - Iraq, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2084)
  - Africa, 1945; 1945/475
    - Africa, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2084)
    - Africa - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/475.R
      - Africa, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2084)
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/475.S
      - Africa, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2084)
  - North Africa Region, 1945; 1945/485
    - Egypt, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2084)
    - North Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/485.E
      - Egypt, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2084)
    - North Africa Region - Yellow Fever, 1945; 1945/485.O
      - Egypt, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2084)
  - South Africa Region, 1945; 1945/487
    - Southern Africa, 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2084)
  - France, 1945; 1945/500
    - France - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2085)
    - France - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 307, Folder 2086)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/500.A
      - France, 1945 (Box 308, Folder 2087)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/500.E
      - France, 1945 (Box 308, Folder 2087)
      - France - Government Fellows, 1945 (Box 308, Folder 2087)
      - France - Government Fellows - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 308, Folder 2088)
      - France - Government Fellows - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 308, Folder 2089)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/500.R
      - France, 1945 (Box 308, Folder 2090)
    - France - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/500.S
      - France, 1945 (Box 308, Folder 2090)
  - China, 1945; 1945/601
    - China - (General), 1945 (Box 308, Folder 2091)
    - China - Administration, 1945 (Box 308, Folder 2092)
    - China - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2093)
    - China - (A-Z), 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2094)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/601.A
      - China, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2095)
    - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/601.D
      - China, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2095)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/601.E
      - China, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2095)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/601.R
      - China, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2095)
    - China - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/601.S
      - China, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2095)
  - Japan, 1945; 1945/609
    - Japan, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2096)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/609.E
      - Japan, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2096)
    - Japan - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/609.S
      - Japan, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2096)
  - Thailand, 1945; 1945/617
    - Thailand, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2096)
  - Holland (Netherlands), 1945; 1945/650
    - Netherlands - (A-R), 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2096)
    - Netherlands - (S-Z), 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2097)
    - Netherlands - (S-Z), 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/650.A
      - Netherlands, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/650.D
      - Netherlands, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/650.R
      - Netherlands, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
    - Holland (Netherlands) - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/650.S
      - Netherlands, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
  - Europe, 1945; 1945/700
    - Europe, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
    - MAK-1 Makinsky, Alexander "Trends Prevailing in Liberated Europe", 1945 (Box 562, Folder 3829)
    - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/700.A
      - Europe, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
    - Europe - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/700.E
      - Europe, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
    - Europe - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/700.S
      - STE-1 Stephan, Frederick F. European Diary, 1945 (Box 562, Folder 3830)
  - Austria, 1945; 1945/705
    - Austria, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
  - Belgium, 1945; 1945/707
    - Belgium, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2098)
    - Belgium - Masiewicz, J., 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2099)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Restricted - Confidential material.
    - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/707.A
      - Belgium, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2100)
    - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/707.R
      - Belgium, 1945 (Box 309, Folder 2100)
  - Zaire, 1945; 1945/709
    - Zaire, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2101)
  - Yugoslavia, 1945; 1945/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2101)
    - Yugoslavia - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/710.A
      - Yugoslavia, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2101)
  - Bulgaria, 1945; 1945/711
    - Bulgaria, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2102)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1945; 1945/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2102)
    - Czechoslovakia - Nursing, 1945; 1945/712.C
      - Czechoslovakia, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2102)
    - Czechoslovakia - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/712.R
      - Czechoslovakia, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2102)
  - Denmark, 1945; 1945/713
    - Denmark, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2102)
    - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/713.R
      - Denmark, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2102)
  - Estonia, 1945; 1945/714
    - Estonia, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2102)
  - Germany, 1945; 1945/717
    - Germany, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2103)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/717.A
      - Germany, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2103)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/717.D
      - Germany, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2103)
    - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/717.R
      - Germany, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2103)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/717.S
      - Germany, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2103)
  - Greece, 1945; 1945/749
    Greece
    - Greece - Malaria, 1945; 1945/749.I
      - Greece, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2104)
  - Hungary, 1945; 1945/750
    - Hungary, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2104)
  - Italy, 1945; 1945/751
    - Italy, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2104)
    - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/751.A
      - Italy, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2104)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/751.E
      - Italy, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2104)
    - Italy - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/751.R
      - Italy, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2104)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/751.S
      - Italy, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2104)
  - Morocco, 1945; 1945/765
    Morocco
    - Morocco, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2105)
  - Norway, 1945; 1945/767
    - Norway, 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2105)
    - Norway - (A-R), 1945 (Box 310, Folder 2106)
    - Norway - (R-Z), 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
    - Norway - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/767.A
      - Norway, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
    - Norway - Nursing, 1945; 1945/767.C
      - Norway, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
    - Norway - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/767.D
      - Norway, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/767.E
      - Norway, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
    - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/767.R
      - Norway, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
  - Iran, 1945; 1945/771
    - Iran, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
  - Portugal, 1945; 1945/773
    - Portugal, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
  - Romania, 1945; 1945/783
    - Romania, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
    - Romania - Declinations, 1945; 1945/783.F
      - Romania, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2107)
  - U.S.S.R., 1945; 1945/785
    - U. S. S. R., 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2108)
    - U.S.S.R. - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/785.A
      - U. S. S. R., 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2108)
    - U.S.S.R. - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1945; 1945/785.D
      - U. S. S. R., 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2108)
    - U.S.S.R. - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/785.R
      - U. S. S. R., 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2108)
      - U. S. S. R., 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2109)
    - U.S.S.R. - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/785.S
      - U. S. S. R., 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2109)
  - Finland, 1945; 1945/787
    - Finland, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2110)
    - Finland - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/787.R
      - Finland, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2110)
  - Poland, 1945; 1945/789
    - Poland, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2110)
    - BAU-1 Bauer, J. H. "Report on the American Red Cross Mission to Poland", 1945 (Box 562, Folder 3831)
    - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/789.A
      - Poland, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2110)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/789.E
      - Poland, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2110)
  - Sweden, 1945; 1945/800
    - Sweden, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2111)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/800.A
      - Sweden, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2111)
    - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1945; 1945/800.R
      - Sweden, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2111)
    - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1945; 1945/800.S
      - Sweden, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2111)
  - Switzerland, 1945; 1945/803
    - Switzerland, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2112)
    - Switzerland - Medical Sciences, 1945; 1945/803.A
      - Switzerland, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2112)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1945; 1945/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2112)
  - Near East Region, 1945; 1945/804
    - Near East Region, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2112)
  - Turkey, 1945; 1945/805
    - Turkey, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2112)
    - Turkey - Nursing, 1945; 1945/805.C
      - Turkey, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2112)
    - Turkey - Malaria, 1945; 1945/805.I
      - Turkey, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2112)
  - Lebanon, 1945; 1945/833
    - Lebanon, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2112)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1945; 1945/833.C
      - Lebanon, 1945 (Box 311, Folder 2112)
- General Correspondence, 1946
  - International, 1946; 1946/100
    - Staff - International - (A), 1946 (Box 312, Folder 2113)
    - Staff - International - (A), 1946 (Box 312, Folder 2114)
    - Staff - International - Balfour, M. C. - 1-3, 1946 (Box 312, Folder 2115)
    - Staff - International - Balfour, M. C. - 1-3, 1946 (Box 312, Folder 2116)
    - Staff - International - Balfour, M. C. - 1-3, 1946 (Box 312, Folder 2117)
    - Staff - International - (Ba), 1946 (Box 312, Folder 2118)
    - Staff - International - (Be), 1946 (Box 313, Folder 2119)
    - Staff - International - (Bl-Bu), 1946 (Box 313, Folder 2120)
    - Staff - International - Carr, Henry P., 1946 (Box 313, Folder 2121)
    - Staff - International - Carr, Henry P. - 1-2, 1946 (Box 313, Folder 2122)
    - Staff - International - Carr, Henry P. - 1-2, 1946 (Box 313, Folder 2123)
    - Staff - International - Carter, Joseph C., 1946 (Box 313, Folder 2124)
    - Staff - International - (Ca-Cr), 1946 (Box 314, Folder 2125)
    - Staff - International - Crawford, P. J., 1946 (Box 314, Folder 2126)
    - Staff - International - (Cr-Di) (Box 314, Folder 2128)
    - Staff - International - Dyer, Brian R. (Box 314, Folder 2129)
    - Staff - International - (E-Fl) (Box 314, Folder 2130)
    - Staff - International - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1946 (Box 315, Folder 2131-2133)
    - Staff - International - (Fo-Gr), 1946 (Box 315, Folder 2134)
    - Staff - International - Grant, John B., 1946 (Box 315, Folder 2135-2137, Box 316, Folder 2138-2139)
    - Staff - International - Hackett, Lewis W., 1946 (Box 316, Folder 2140-2141)
    - Staff - International - Hahn, R.G. and Haynes, Guy S., 1946 (Box 316, Folder 2142)
    - Staff - International - Hill, Rolla B., 1946 (Box 316, Folder 2143)
    - Staff - International - Hirst, Esther Mary, 1946 (Box 317, Folder 2144)
    - Staff - International - (Hi-I), 1946 (Box 317, Folder 2145-2146)
    - Staff - International - Janney, John H., 1946 (Box 317, Folder 2147-2149)
    - Staff - International - Johnson, Harold N., 1946 (Box 317)
    - Staff - International - Kendrick, John F., 1946 (Box 318)
    - Staff - International - Kerr, J. Austin, 1946 (Box 318, Folder 2152)
    - Staff - International - Kitchen, Stuart F., 1946 (Box 318, Folder 2153)
    - Staff - International - Kittredge, Tracy B.; Lambert, Robert A.; Lambert, S. M. (Box 318, Folder 2154)
    - Staff - International - Leach, Charles N., 1946 (Box 318, Folder 2155-2157)
    - Staff - International - (Le), 1946 (Box 318, Folder 2158)
    - Staff - International - Logan, John A., 1946 (Box 319, Folder 2159)
    - Staff - International - McCoy, O. R., 1946 (Box 319, Folder 2160)
    - Staff - International - McIntosh, W. A., 1946 (Box 319, Folder 2161)
    - Staff - International - Magoon, E. H., 1946 (Box 319, Folder 2162)
    - Staff - International - Maier, John, 1946 (Box 319, Folder 2163)
    - Staff - International - (Ma), 1946 (Box 319, Folder 2164)
    - Staff - International - Microphotography, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 2165)
    - Staff - International - Millery, W.; Morison, Robert S.; Mosely, Philip, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 2166)
    - Staff - International - Muench, Hugo, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 2167)
    - Staff - International - (No-Pa), 1946 (Box 320, Folder 2168)
    - Staff - International - Paul, J. H., 1946 (Box 320, Folder 2169)
    - Staff - International - Payne, George C.; Penicillin, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 2170)
    - Staff - International - Peterson, Osler L.; Plague, 1946 (Box 320, Folder 2171)
    - Staff - International - (Po-Ra), 1946 (Box 321)
    - Staff - International - Richard, E. R.; Reihl, L. A.; Riley, Edwin, G., 1946 (Box 321, Folder 2173)
    - Staff - International - Russell, Paul F., 1946 (Box 321, Folder 2174)
    - Staff - International - (Sa-Sm), 1946 (Box 321, Folder 2175)
    - Staff - International - Smithburn, Kenneth C., 1946 (Box 321, Folder 2176-2777)
    - Staff - International - Stevens, David H.; Soper, Fred L., 1946 (Box 322, Folder 2178)
    - Staff - International - Strode, George K., 1946 (Box 322, Folder 2179)
    - Staff - International - Sweet, W. C.; Taylor, Richard M., 1946 (Box 322, Folder 2180)
    - Staff - International - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1946 (Box 322, Folder 2181-2182)
    - Staff - International - Theiler, Max; Thompson, Norma S., 1946 (Box 322, Folder 2183)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - A-Z (Persons), 1946 (Box 322, Folder 2184)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - A-Z (Organizations), 1946 (Box 322, Folder 2185)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO, 1946 (Box 323, Folder 2186)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO (A-Z), 1946 (Box 323, Folder 2187)
    - Staff - International - United States - Warren, 1946 (Box 323, Folder 2188)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert B., 1946 (Box 323, Folder 2189-2190)
    - Staff - International - Weaver, Warren; Weir, John M., 1946 (Box 323, Folder 2191)
    - Staff - International - Wells, Clifford W., 1946 (Box 324, Folder 2192)
    - Staff - International - (Wh-Wi), 1946 (Box 324, Folder 2193)
    - Staff - Wilson, David B., 1946 (Box 324, Folder 2194-2195)
    - Staff - International - (Wo-Z), 1946 (Box 324, Folder 2196)
    - International - Nursing, 1946; 1946/100.C
      - Staff - International, 1946 (Box 324, Folder 2197)
    - International - Hookworm, 1946; 1946/100.H
      - Staff - International, 1946 (Box 324, Folder 2198)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1946; 1946/100.O
      - Staff - International, 1946 (Box 324, Folder 2198)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1946; 1946/100.S
      - Staff - International, 1946 (Box 324, Folder 2198)
    - International - Tuberculosis, 1946; 1946/100.T
      - Staff - International, 1946 (Box 324, Folder 2198)
  - United States, 1946; 1946/200
    - United States - (A-American Association), 1946 (Box 325, Folder 2199)
    - United States - (American Board for Medical Aid to China), 1946 (Box 325, Folder 2200)
    - United States - (American Board for Medical Aid to China - Reports), 1946 (Box 325, Folder 2201)
    - United States - (American C-D), 1946 (Box 325, Folder 2202)
    - United States - American Economic Association, 1946 (Box 325, Folder 2203)
    - United States - (American E-P), 1946 (Box 325, Folder 2204)
    - United States - (American R-Ar), 1946 (Box 326, Folder 2205)
    - United States - (American As-Az), 1946 (Box 326, Folder 2206)
    - United States - (B-Bo), 1946 (Box 326, Folder 2207)
    - United States - (Br-Car), 1946 (Box 326, Folder 2208)
    - United States - Carnegie Endowment - Atomic Energy, 1946 (Box 326, Folder 2209)
    - United States - (Caro-Col), 1946 (Box 326, Folder 2210)
    - United States - (Com-Cor), 1946 (Box 327, Folder 2211)
    - United States - (Cor-Da), 1946 (Box 327, Folder 2212)
    - United States - (De-Do), 1946 (Box 327, Folder 2213)
    - United States - (Dr-Dz), 1946 (Box 327, Folder 2214)
    - United States - (E), 1946 (Box 327, Folder 2215)
    - United States - (F), 1946 (Box 327, Folder 2216)
    - United States - (G-Ge), 1946 (Box 328, Folder 2217)
    - United States - (Gi-Gz), 1946 (Box 328, Folder 2218)
    - United States - (Ha), 1946 (Box 328, Folder 2219)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 328, Folder 2220)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-Z), 1946 (Box 328, Folder 2221)
    - United States - (Ha-Hz), 1946 (Box 328, Folder 2222)
    - United States - (I-In), 1946 (Box 329, Folder 2223)
    - United States - (In-J), 1946 (Box 329, Folder 2224)
    - United States - (K), 1946 (Box 329, Folder 2225)